{
  "question": "When I fight, I like to...",
  "options": [
    {
      "answer": "Hit them where it hurts -- physically.",
      "question": "What's your view on personal space?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "I don't have boundaries.",
          "question": "You do that by being really fast?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Nope, just by being really close.",
              "question": "Like REALLY close?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Close enough to sink a knife in.",
                  "reRoute": {
                    "keySequence": [ 0, 1, 0 ]
                  }
                },
                {
                  "answer": "REALLY close.",
                  "class": "barbarian"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Pretty close, yeah.",
                  "question": "You like having tools to stay close?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "I love tools.",
                      "question": "Tools as in...",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Weapons.",
                          "question": "Like, EVERY weapon?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "What do I look like?",
                              "class": "fighter"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Tools. Like lockpicks, grappling hooks, crowbars.",
                          "question": "Crowbars are a weapon.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Shut up.",
                              "class": "rogue"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I prefer just myself.",
                      "question": "Fast feet?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Sonic's my name, baby.",
                          "question": "Get away from my table.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "I'm sorry.",
                              "question": "Good, let's try that again.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "...",
                                  "reRoute": {
                                    "keySequence" : [ 0, 0, 0, 2, 1 ]
                                  }
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Sonic is good!",
                              "question": "Oh man. Rocks fell. You died.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Try again?",
                                  "reset": true
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Actually, no, they're just big feet.",
                          "question": "You're a pretty big guy.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Compared to you.",
                              "class": "barbarian"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "What?",
                              "question": "It's from Batman.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Oh, sorry. Been a while since I've seen it.",
                                  "question": "Go watch it, then restart.",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "Done!",
                                      "reset": true
                                    }
                                  ]
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "Never watched Batman.",
                                  "duplicatePath": {
                                    "index": 0
                                  }
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Yeah, pretty fast.",
                          "class": "monk"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "I once ran a marathon in twelve seconds.",
              "question": "Usain Bolt a role model?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Of course he is.",
                  "class": "monk"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Not really.",
                  "fakeOut": "You know that isn't true."
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Nope, just by sneakin' up right on ya.",
              "reRoute": {
                "keySequence" : [ 0, 1, 0 ]
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Respectable, but close when I need to be.",
          "question": "You an animal kind of person?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Not really.",
              "question": "You like sneakin' around?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "I could give or take it.",
                  "question": "You could give or take a lot of things, huh?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "I guess.",
                      "class": "fighter"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Nuh-uh! I'm passionate about stuff!",
                      "question": "Really? Name one thing.",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "...",
                          "question": "That's what I thought.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "...",
                              "class": "fighter"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Me!",
                          "question": "Got a magical bone in your body?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Several, now that we mention it.",
                              "class": "sorcerer"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Only magic here is from my sick songs!",
                              "class": "bard"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "God!",
                          "question": "Do you like hitting things for your god?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Of course.",
                              "question": "Do \"things\" include anyone who doesn't believe in your god?",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "What are you implying?",
                                  "question": "Nothing.",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "...",
                                      "class": "paladin"
                                    }
                                  ]
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "What kind of question is that?",
                                  "question": "Nevermind.",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "...",
                                      "class": "paladin"
                                    }
                                  ]
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "No, and they don't either. They're very loving.",
                              "question": "No, and they don't either. They're very loving.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Are you just saying that because sometimes he answers your calls?",
                                  "question": "Gods can do that?",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "Yours can!",
                                      "class": "cleric"
                                    }
                                  ]
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "Actually, it's a \"she,\" and it's Mother Earth.",
                                  "question": "Actually, we're not on earth. But I'll let that slide.",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "...",
                                      "class": "druid"
                                    }
                                  ]
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "I wouldn't really call it a \"God\" actually...",
                              "question": "Let me guess, is it some crazy spirit thing?",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Yes.",
                                  "question": "That gave you magical powers?",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "Yeah.",
                                      "question": "What's your opinion on the word \"Eldritch\"?",
                                      "options": [
                                        {
                                          "answer": "I could say it every six seconds.",
                                          "question": "I'll keep you to that.",
                                          "options": [
                                            {
                                              "answer": "...",
                                              "class": "warlock"
                                            }
                                          ]
                                        },
                                        {
                                          "answer": "I'm pretty sure, by definition, that's what the thing is.",
                                          "class": "warlock"
                                        }
                                      ]
                                    }
                                  ]
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "I'm doing that as we speak",
                  "question": "You'll love this.",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "...",
                      "class": "rogue"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Absolutely.",
              "question": "Like, so much you want to be one?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "I prefer them as pets...",
                  "class": "ranger"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Is that an option?",
                  "class": "druid"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Please get away from me.",
          "question": "What's Katniss Everdeen to you?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "A role model!",
              "class": "ranger"
            },
            {
              "answer": "She should have used a gun...",
              "question": "We don't have guns. Would a hand crossbow work?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yeah, that's fine",
                  "class": "rogue"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Absolutely not.",
                  "question": "What's your opinion on \"canon\"?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Great to blow things up with",
                      "question": "Was that a pun?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "No. What's a pun?",
                          "question": "...Did you mean to go to the \"Up close\" flow?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "...Yeah.",
                              "class": "barbarian"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "No, I'm where I belong.",
                              "class": "fighter"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Heh, yeah.",
                          "question": "Do you want to actually blow things up?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Do I even have to say it?",
                              "class": "artificer"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I don't need to be officially recognized.",
                      "class": "artificer"
                    }
                  ]
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Who?",
              "question": "You sound like a nerd. Sure you don't like magic?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "No, I'm certain",
                  "question": "What about magic that doesn't leave you vulnerable?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Still no.",
                      "question": "Oh. You're not a nerd. You're just not... \"book smart.\"",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Nope.",
                          "question": "You just like saying \"no\" to things, huh?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "No.",
                              "question": "Say no again.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "No.",
                                  "question": "Do you even want to play?",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "No.",
                                      "question": "Go grab a pizza.",
                                      "options": [
                                        {
                                          "answer": "Start Over.",
                                          "reset": true
                                        }
                                      ]
                                    },
                                    {
                                      "answer": "Yeah.",
                                      "question": "Do you just like messing with me?",
                                      "options": [
                                        {
                                          "answer": "Yeah.",
                                          "class": "bard"
                                        },
                                        {
                                          "answer": "No.",
                                          "fakeOut": "Yeah, you do."
                                        }
                                      ]
                                    }
                                  ]
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "Nah.",
                                  "duplicatePath": {
                                    "index": 0
                                  }
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Lol, yeah.",
                              "question": "You sound like an asshole.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "...",
                                  "class": "bard"
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Right.",
                          "question": "Axes or swords?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Axes.",
                              "class": "barbarian"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Swords.",
                              "class": "fighter"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "I'm interested.",
                      "question": "Which sounds most appealing?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "God",
                          "question": "Damage or utility?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Damage",
                              "class": "paladin"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "Utility",
                              "class": "cleric"
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Devils",
                          "class": "warlock"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Trees",
                          "question": "Do you want to BE a tree?",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "That's weird.",
                              "question": "Yeah, kinda.",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "...",
                                  "class": "ranger"
                                }
                              ]
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "That's an option?",
                              "class": "druid"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "I might have changed my mind... Let's go with magic afterall.",
                  "reRoute": {
                    "keySequence": [ 1 ]
                  }
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "Use magic to weaken them in ways previously unimaginable.",
      "question": "How beefy do you like being?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "Honestly, if I get sneezed on, it might be too late.",
          "question": "Picture your perfect toolbox. It's basically...",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "You stole these tools from an abomination that might destroy the world",
              "question": "This analogy isn't going very well.",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Nothing else goes very well.",
                  "class": "warlock"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Full to the bri of tools you bought, found, and learned. Nerd.",
              "class": "wizard"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Pristine quality over quantity that you've just always had. Jock.",
              "class": "sorcerer"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Given to you from your church, they prayed away your poor health.",
              "question": "How do you view hammers?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Someone might get hurt :(",
                  "question": "Don't let them tell you it's your fault when you fix their boo-boos, okay?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Okay",
                      "class": "cleric"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "I might get someone hurt :)",
                  "class": "paladin"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "A little, nothing major.",
          "question": "What if you could turn into an elephant, be REALLY beefy?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "But then I'd be ugly!",
              "question": "Okay...",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "pretty boy",
                  "class": "bard"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "What the hell? That sounds awesome.",
              "question": "Is only being able to do it twice a day a deal breaker?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yeah...",
                  "question": "What if you worshipped a godly elephant instead?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "That'd be lit.",
                      "question": "Is your elephant god popular?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Totally.",
                          "question": "Get to preachin'!",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Will do!",
                              "class": "cleric"
                            },
                            {
                              "answer": "I don't want to preach!",
                              "question": "What DO you want?",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "To... smite?",
                                  "class": "paladin"
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "To... punch it?",
                                  "class": "monk"
                                },
                                {
                                  "answer": "To... do a little bit of everything, none of it very well, and be extremely confusing to everyone?",
                                  "class": "mystic"
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Only I know he exists.",
                          "question": "Hippy.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "Whatever",
                              "class": "warlock"
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Can I hunt it?",
                      "question": "You'd want to?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Yeah",
                          "class": "ranger"
                        }
                      ]
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Not at all.",
                  "class": "druid"
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Me big.",
          "question": "You charming?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "*picks nose*",
              "question": "I... don't trust you around magic.",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Me understand",
                  "class": "barbarian"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "It's like I'm from a fairy tale.",
              "class": "paladin"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "answer": "Either stop the fight, or end it quickly by helping my friends.",
      "question": "What does \"utility\" mean to you?",
      "options": [
        {
          "answer": "The folks who fix my water pipes.",
          "question": "You think you're funny?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "No.",
              "question": "Kinda dense?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "Yeah",
                  "question": "Like to go the long way around?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "question": "Through cities or nature?",
                      "options": [
                        {
                          "answer": "Cities",
                          "class": "rogue"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Nature",
                          "class": "druid"
                        },
                        {
                          "answer": "Option #3",
                          "question": "Doesn't exist.",
                          "options": [
                            {
                              "answer": "I'd like to make it exist.",
                              "question": "Are you certain?",
                              "options": [
                                {
                                  "answer": "Absolutely.",
                                  "question": "You won't like it.",
                                  "options": [
                                    {
                                      "answer": "I'm ready.",
                                      "question": "DM",
                                      "options": [
                                        {
                                          "answer": "I wasn't ready.",
                                          "reset": true
                                        }
                                      ]
                                    }
                                  ]
                                }
                              ]
                            }
                          ]
                        }
                      ]
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "fakeOut": "You just did."
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "duplicatePath": {
                    "index": 0
                  }
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "Yeah.",
              "class": "bard"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Eighty billion options.",
          "question": "For how many spells?",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "Eighty billion spells.",
              "class": "wizard"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Four.",
              "class": "sorcerer"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "answer": "Praying the Dying Away",
          "question": "Praying to...",
          "options": [
            {
              "answer": "My great friend, God!",
              "class": "cleric"
            },
            {
              "answer": "It's... sorta a god.",
              "question": "Do you fully understand it?",
              "options": [
                {
                  "answer": "No",
                  "question": "Do you want to?",
                  "options": [
                    {
                      "answer": "No",
                      "class": "warlock"
                    },
                    {
                      "answer": "Yes",
                      "fakeOut": "No you don't"
                    }
                  ]
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Yes",
                  "fakeOut": "No you don't"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "answer": "The Holy Retributioner, Also God",
              "class": "paladin"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}